Let's begin our exploration of the AI
fluency
让我们开始探索 AI 流畅度
framework. I'm Joe Feller. My name is
框架 我是 Joe Feller 我的名字是
Drew. I'm Maggie Vo. My name is Rick
Drew 我是 Maggie Vo 我的名字是 Rick
Dacon. The focus of this course is not
Dacon 这门课程的重点并不是
really about AI as a technology.
真正讨论 AI 这项技术
Instead, it's mostly about you and I, us
相反 它主要讨论你和我 我们
humans, and how we interact and
人类 以及我们如何与 AI 互动并
collaborate with AI systems. We explore
协作 我们会探索
AI fluency, our ability to engage with
AI 流畅度 也就是我们与
AI systems in ways that are effective,
AI 系统互动的能力 方式要做到有效
efficient, ethical, and safe. It's about
高效 合乎伦理且安全 这关乎
imagining possibilities that don't treat
想象各种可能性 而不是把
AI as some sort of next level spellch
AI 当成某种升级版拼写检查器
checker, but instead as a trusted
而是把它视为值得信赖的
partner for doing creative and
创意和
innovative problem solving work. This
创新性问题解决工作的伙伴 这
will help you develop an intuitive feel
将帮助你培养直觉般的感受
for what generative AI can do and how
了解生成式 AI 能做什么 以及
best to work with it. We're all learning
如何最好地与它协作 我们都在学习
together how to navigate this rapidly
如何共同应对这片快速
evolving landscape. This course is about
不断演变的领域 这门课程旨在
fundamentally shifting how we approach
从根本上改变我们处理
AI.
AI 的方式